Muhammad Ilham Haqqi

Central Java. Indonesia



ilhamserbaguna@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/hagger

Summary

Experienced Information Technology Support Technician with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Python and Javascript, Web Applications, RESTful WebServices, and REST API. Strong information technology professional graduated from Universitas Dian Nuswantoro.

Experience

Software Engineer

Azura Labs

Oct 2021 - Present (1 year 9 months)

IT Support Technician

Dinas Penataan Ruang Kota Semarang

Mar 2019 - Present (4 years 4 months)

Created Distaru API Service, integrating DISTARU AP Service with Bappenda Payment gateway

Software Engineer

Azura Labs

Sep 2019 - Oct 2021 (2 years 2 months)

work mostly as Backend Engineer, working with Golang and gRPC also with NodeJS

FLS Full Stack Developer

Future Leader Summit

Apr 2019 - Sep 2019 (6 months)

Develop App registration and Organization, also prepare and setup web service

Education



📵 Universitas Dian Nuswantoro

Teknologi Informasi 2017 - 2023

Skills

PHP • Web Development • Web Services • Web Applications • JavaScript • REST APIs • Linux • Network Engineering • Docker • Go (Programming Language)